I lied to my
family about being at
an NBA game on
Christmas, but instead I
spent the day with
my dogs. My brother
caused a scene at
Thanksgiving, it was pretty
intense. He's always been
a problem child, and
I think he struggles
with bipolar disorder without
proper treatment. It's really
hard to watch him
go through this. He's
34 to 35 years
old, for years older
than me, and his
life has just been
one issue after another.
He had learning disabilities,
drove recklessly as a
teenager, and even smoked
marijuana in his car
on the way to
school. He's obsessed with
our relationship, trying to
fix it for the
past few years. I'm
nice to him, but
he takes everything personally.
Before Thanksgiving, I studied
up on how to
deal with highly insecure
people, but that didn't
make a difference. The
smallest thing sets him
off, and he picks
on me mercilessly. I
was 30 years old,
so I tried to
shut it down at
the gathering, barely speaking
to anyone. He ended
up threatening my younger
cousins for no reason,
just because they left
after he got upset.
My aunt stepped in,
telling our family that
he's not welcome around
our cousins again. I've
tried explaining this situation
to them before, they
know what's going on,
but don't know how
to help. So when
it came up at
Christmas, I told them
straight out, if he's
coming over, I'm not
going to deal with
it. They were upset,
and my aunt even
contacted our grandma to
convince him to change.
Then I got invited
to spend Christmas with
him, his wife, and
my sister, which included
my niece. I told
them I wasn't comfortable
around him, given his
bipolar disorder, the fact
that he doesn't take
medication, and what happened
at Thanksgiving. They didn't
listen or think I
was bluffing. I saw
an NBA game on
TV that year and
told everyone I was
going to the game,
but instead, I stayed
home with my dogs
for a stress -free
Christmas holiday for the
first time in five
years. I've decided not
to see or have
contact with him for
quite some time.