I met my wits
end. My husband and
I have been together
for eight years, married
for just one now,
and we've had sex
only once in the
past two years, since
our daughter was born,
to be exact. We
want intimacy back, but
it feels like a
distant dream. Our daughter
is 17 months old,
premature at birth, and
spent two weeks in
the NICU. When she
came home, I asked
my parents not to
visit her, due to
health concerns for my
severe preeclampsia. But they
showed up anyway, forcing
their way into the
hospital room. When I
tried to limit visitors,
they called me manipulative.
Now, my husband is
saying the same things,
that I'm vindictive and
keeping our grandchild away.
This isn't just about
our daughter's visitations, it's
about feeling like a
roommate in our own
home. My husband doesn't
defend me emotionally, even
when I need him
most. Like when my
dad passed away, he
waited two days before
showing up to comfort
me after playing tennis
with his best friend.
The lack of intimacy
is suffocating. We've tried
sending flirty texts, but
he just laughs them
off. He says he's
too busy working and
providing for us financially,
but that doesn't feel
like an excuse when
our marriage is struggling.
I'm trying to salvage
what's left of our
relationship with the help
of a marital counselor.
But every time I
bring up issues, it
feels like throwing words
at a wall. I
want to feel wanted
by my husband again,
but he seems too
caught up in his
own world. Is this
relationship even worth saving,
or is it just
slowly crashing?