I work at a
liquor store on Christmas
Day, which is usually
pretty slow. As my
shift drew to a
close, I and my
coworker were bored out
of our minds, so
we started having fun.
We took turns scanning
the same tiny bottle
of alcohol, just to
keep the joke going.
Then, we decided to
take it up a
notch. My coworker scanned
an entire box of
pre -made shooters, 40
of them at $3
each, several times, adding
to the total. By
then, our running tally
was something like $2
,500. We were cracking
up, and it was
clear we'd done enough
to entertain ourselves. My
coworker had a bright
idea to check the
system and see if
there were any expensive
wines left on sale.
He found one worth
almost $10 ,000 and
set the quantity to
$999, the maximum allowed.
Our total jumped to
around $9 million, and
we were still in
stitches. Things took a
turn for the worse
when my coworker spotted
another bottle worth nearly
$20 ,000. He added
it to the system,
setting the quantity to
$999 again, which brought
our total up to
around $28 million. That's
when I made a
mistake, I let out
a bit too much
laughter and pretended to
bring the transaction to
the point where we'd
confirmed the cash price.
But in that moment
of distraction, my coworker
didn't see me there,
and he accidentally pressed
enter, completing the transaction.
Suddenly, $28 million was
sitting in our cash
register's balance. I immediately
yelled at him to
figure out what had
happened, and his eyes
went wide with realization.
We knew we had
to reverse the entire
thing, but our system
only allows a maximum
of $1 million returns
at a time, so
it took us dozens
of attempts to get
every bottle back onto
the shelves. Now, as
I wait for my
store manager to come
in tomorrow, I'm bracing
myself for an explanation.
We know we messed
up, and our joke
has put our store's
stats and graphs in
jeopardy. Please keep your
fingers crossed for me,
I've accepted that we
deserve some kind of
punishment for our actions.
My boss was understandably
frustrated and disappointed, but
thankfully, it looks like
the worst case scenario
is just warnings or
a notation in our
files.