I just paid off
our house two weeks
ago, a huge milestone
for us. We withdrew
some money from my
retirement accounts, which meant
no taxes on the
withdrawals, a nice bonus.
Now we're starting home
projects and saving 25
% of our income
for retirement. By our
age and salary, that's
already quite impressive. But
I'm not sharing this
with many people. As
someone in finance who's
managed to live comfortably
without going overboard, it's
hard for me to
keep this quiet. I
feel like screaming from
the rooftops, I can
afford it. And I
will retire at 62,
a goal I've been
working towards for years.
I'm not looking for
validation or sympathy, I
just want to share
my excitement and gratitude
with anyone who listen.
Thank you for being
part of this moment.