I'm still trying to
process a pretty intense
encounter with my mom.
It happened three weeks
ago, and I'm not
sure if she caught
me doing what I
was doing, I've been
masturbating in my room
quite frequently. I was
in the middle of
it when my door
suddenly opened. My mom
was standing there, and
at first, I thought
nothing of it because
we were discussing dinner
plans. But then she
said a few words
and quickly pulled the
covers back up, like
she just realized something.
To try to diffuse
the situation, I tried
to keep talking about
food, what we could
have for dinner or
grab from the fridge.
She answered my questions
without batting an eye,
which was weird because
normally she wouldn't ask
me what I was
doing when she walked
in on me. In
fact, it's not even
a normal occurrence that
she knocks before coming
into my room. It's
been happening every time
we have the door
closed for weeks now.