I'm not as embarrassed
as the title would
suggest. To set the
record straight, this happened
on Christmas Day, not
today. So, after a
few too many candles
from my Tannenbaum, I
asked my partner if
they'd like to try
some wax play. I
had been meaning to
get around to it
for a while, and
the holiday season just
sparked my interest again.
My partner eagerly agreed,
and we settled in.
We discussed where to
apply the heat, I
offered to start with
my stomach, and lit
the candle. The anticipation
built up, and I
couldn't help but chuckle
at how much I
used to enjoy dipping
my fingers in wax
as a kid. Just
as things were getting
interesting, I heard a
loud noise and felt
a cinderland on my
skin. I let out
an involuntary yelp, and
my partner quickly extinguished
the candle. But it
wasn't about me being
startled, that's when I
turned to see our
giant orange cat standing
in the doorway, staring
at us with an
unnerving intensity. Our normally
timid pet was being
its usual intimidating self,
completely unfazed by the
sudden noise. It's a
cat who hides from
the vacuum cleaner and
screams for wet food,
but also happens to
be terrified of his
own shadow. After calming
our nervous partner down,
the cat slowly backed
away and left us
alone. Needless to say,
things took a bit
of a delay in
getting back on track.
I've learned that if
I want to dip
into wax again, I
need to make sure
the door is shut,
or risk our orange
tom thinking we're being
attacked and going wild.
The moral of this
story. Avoid making loud
noises around your cat
when you're trying to
be intimate, trust me
on this one.