I'll never forget what
happened at my uncle's
house that Christmas. When
I was 11 years
old, my parents were
still together, but they
were getting ready to
split. My dad stayed
with my uncle, and
we would spend our
school holidays there. The
house had a great
setup for guests, a
two -story design with
a granny flat downstairs
that could sleep multiple
people. I remember having
slumber parties downstairs with
my cousins every evening,
while the adults drank
upstairs and watched TV
or played games. One
night, things took a
dark turn. My parents
and several others were
drinking upstairs, while my
cousins and I were
getting ready for bed.
My dad stumbled down
to the granny flat,
passed out on the
double bed, and soon
fell asleep. That's when
my mom came downstairs,
started touching him, trying
to kiss him. He
told her to stop,
but she didn't listen.
She climbed on top
of him, and I'm
still trying to process
what happened next. The
sounds, the smells, it's
all so vivid in
my mind. My dad
tried to leave, but
she threatened to hurt
me if I left,
too. My cousins fled
the scene, and I
rolled over, crying. The
next morning, I woke
up alone in the
flat. My dad was
hungover, and my uncle
confronted my mom and
dad about what had
happened. He warned them
that if they ever
did something like that
again, he'd beat them
senseless. Then, my mom
cornered me, telling me
I was a pervert,
sick, and a slut,
all because she was
trying to cover up
her own actions. As
an adult now, I
wish my uncle had
taken things further. My
mom's behavior was twisted,
trying to shift the
blame onto me for
something that wasn't mine.
I often wonder if
she was trying to
get pregnant again just
to keep him from
leaving her.